迈克:哦,你们好.
Mike: Oh hi guys.
麦琪:你好,迈克.
Maggie: Hi Mike.
杰森:很好,你来得真不巧,我们刚刚吃完晚饭.
Jason: Well, your timing is terrible. We just finished dinner.
迈克:哦,上帝.我忘记了这是吃饭时间,我工作了一整天,做我的英语学期论文.
Mike: Oh gosh. I didn't even realize it was dinner time. I've been working all day on my English term paper.
麦琪:整天?
Maggie: All day?
迈克:是的,差不多.我需要休息,我想出去,开车兜兜风,让我大脑清醒一下,然后准备熬一个通宵.
Mike: Yeah, pretty much. Boy do I need a break. I think I'll just go out and drive my car a little bit. Kind of clear out my head and then settle in for another all-nighter.
麦琪和杰森:呃!
Maggie and Jason: Uh hu!
迈克:是的,就是这样.我只是想过来问候一下.
Mike: Yeah. Yes, that's pretty much it. Just wanted to stop in and say hi.
杰森:好的.
Jason: Ok.
迈克:哦,天哪.我想我车没油了.我可以借些钱吗?
Mike: Oh darn. I think I'm out of gas. Can I borrow a few bucks?
麦琪和杰森:再见!
Maggie and Jason: Bingo!
迈克:什么?我是说我需要休息一下.
Mike: What? Well all I said was that I needed a little study break.
杰森:好的,你真正需要的就是钱.我敢说你甚至还没开始写你的学期论文呢?
Jason: Yeah, what you really needed was money. I bet you haven't even started writing that term paper yet?
迈克:你是在暗示这是一种……什么词来着?花样.
Mike: Are you suggesting that this is some kind of...What's the word? Con.
杰森:我不是暗示,迈克,我是明说的.
Jason: I'm not suggesting that Mike. I'm flat out saying it.
开萝尔:迈克,什么风把你吹来这儿?钱还是吃的?
Carol: Mike, what brings you here? Money or food?
迈克:你们看看你们培养了什么样的女儿?我是说你们对于我的基本尊重都被这个滑稽的女人给搞没了.
Mike: You see how you are raising your daughter? I mean your basic disrespect for me is rubbing off on the geek woman here.
开萝尔:我需要去初级大学图书馆为我的读书报告作一些调查,我今晚能借你的车吗?
Carol: I need to do some research for my book report at the Junior college library. So could I borrow the car tonight?
杰森:当然可以,哦,我的沃尔沃还在修理店呢.
Jason: Sure. Oh, my Volvo's in the shop.
麦琪:没问题,开萝尔.你可以用我的车.
Maggie: that's ok Carol. You can use my car.
杰森:最好带一些钱,万一没油了.
Jason: Better take some money for gas. Just incase.
迈克:二十块!
Mike: Twenty bucks!
麦琪:小心点,宝贝.
Maggie: Be careful honey.
开萝尔:我要走了,再见.
Carol: I will. Bye.
迈克:很好,很好.这到底是怎么回事?我连几块钱都得不到,但是你们给了20块钱,还有一部车!
Mike: Alright. Alright. Now what the heck is going on here? I mean I can't even get a couple of lousy bucks for gas, but you give her twenty bucks and a car!
杰森:你自己想呢?
Jason: Makes you think, doesn't it?
迈克:不,我不想.
Mike: No, Nothing makes me think.
麦琪:区别就在于,迈克,我们相信开萝尔是去图书馆学习.
Maggie: The difference is Mike, we actually believe Carol is going to the library to study.
迈克:哦,你们是说,如果我去图书馆,你们也会给我钱?
Mike: Oh, so you mean like, if I was going to go to the library, you'd give me money too?
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: Uh hu.
迈克:我确实是去那儿,我不是早就说了吗?我保证我说了,很高兴我们说清楚了.五块,我只要五块.
Mike: Well that's exactly where I was heading. Didn't I mention that earlier? Boy I was sure I did. Glad we cleared that up. A five. All I get is a five!
杰森:你的车更小.
Jason: Smaller car.
桑迪:我看见你在……
Sandy: So, I see you're...
迈克:开萝尔!
Mike: Carol!
开萝尔:迈克,你到底要干嘛?
Carol: Mike. What he hell do you want?
迈克:嘘!你是在图书馆.
Mike: Sh! You're in a library.
开萝尔:你来图书馆干什么?
Carol: What are you doing in a library?
迈克:好的,我最终考虑要见个人,所以我过来了.不管怎样,爸爸妈妈问起你我是否在这儿时,告诉他们你见到了我.好了,我要走了.
Mike: Well, I figured eventually I'd have to see the inside of one, so I thought I'd get it out of the way. Anyway, when mum and dad ask you if you if I was here, tell them you saw me. Alright, I'm out of here.
开萝尔:但是你的学期论文呢?
Carol: But what about your term paper?
迈克:实际上我还没开始呢.
Mike: I didn't actually have one.
开萝尔:你为什么要告诉爸爸妈妈那些呢?
Carol: Well what did you tell mum and dad you did for?
迈克:我需要几块钱,嗯,我不能直接向妈妈要,那不是我的风格.再见.
Mike: Well, I needed a couple of extra bucks and, um, I couldn't just ask mum straight out. It's not my style. See ya.
桑迪:哦,对不起.
Sandy: Ohhh. Sorry.
开萝尔:是我不好.
Carol: Excuse me.
桑迪:那是我的错.
Guy: It was my fault.
开萝尔:没关系.
Carol: It's ok.
桑迪:我只是在找乔伊斯.
Sandy: I was just looking for Joyce.
开萝尔:哦.
Carol: Oh.
桑迪:詹姆斯?乔伊斯.
Sandy: James Joyce.
开萝尔:我不知道他们在哪儿,我不是这所学校的.
Carol: Oh. I don't know where they keep them. I don't go to this school.
桑迪:哦,真的.你上的哪所大学?
Sandy: Oh really. What college do you go to?
开萝尔:大学?纽大学,你呢?
Carol: College? NYU, you?
桑迪:就一个纽?
Sandy: Isn't there just one 'u'?
开萝尔:不,我是说纽约大学,你上的是哪个?
Carol: No, I meant NYU, where do you go?
桑迪:哦,我就在这儿,大二.你喜欢F 斯科特 菲茨杰拉德吗?
Sandy: Oh. Well I go here. Sophomore. So, I see you are a fan of F Scott Fitzgerald's.
开萝尔:哦,我在写一篇关于的文章.
Carol: Oh, I'm doing a paper on "Tender is the Night".
桑迪:哦,那是一本好书.
Sandy: Oh, what a great book.
开萝尔:我知道.那是一个伤感的故事,非常的浪漫,我喜欢这个主题,移居国外的人坐在咖啡馆,品尝美酒,谈论着艺术,生活和爱情.
Carol: I know. It's such a sad story. It's so romantic. Love the idea of expatriates' sitting in a cafe. Sipping good wine, talking about art and life and love.
桑迪:想喝啤酒吗?
Sandy: Want to get a beer?
开萝尔:哦?
Carol: Hu?
桑迪:我很抱歉,有点冒失,我的名字叫桑迪.
Sandy: Oh, I'm sorry. That was a little abrupt. My name's Sandy.
开萝尔:我是开萝尔.
Carol: I'm Carol.
桑迪:你好.
Sandy: Hi.
开萝尔:你好.
Carol: Hi.
桑迪:我只是想休息一下,你愿意和我去街道对面的科格啤酒屋吗?
Sandy: Well I was just thinking of taking a study break and I wondered if you wanted to go with me across the street to the Beer Keg.
开萝尔:我,去科格啤酒屋?
Carol: Me, go to the Beer Keg?
桑迪:是的,他们也有葡萄酒,我们可以在那谈论爱情,艺术,生活以及巴黎.
Sandy: Well they have wine too. We could talk about love and art and life and Paris.
开萝尔:哦,听起来很不错,但是我有很多事要做.
Carol: Oh gee, it sounds great, but I have a lot of work to do.
桑迪:哦!好的,也许可以换个时间.
Sandy: Oh! Right. Well maybe some other time.
开萝尔:还是现在吧?
Carol: How about right now?
桑迪:哦,你非常果断.
Sandy: Boy, you are very decisive.
开萝尔:纽约大学的女人都是这样.
Carol: All women are at NYUU.
开萝尔:迈克,迈克,我需要你的建议.
Carol: Mike, Mike. I need your advice.
迈克:哦,这不是做梦吧?
Mike: Oh. Is this a dream?
开萝尔:我知道闯进来很冒失,但我实在无能为力了.
Carol: I know it's a pathetic situation to be in, but I'm desperate.
迈克:哦,这不是梦,这是一场恶梦.
Mike: Oh, this isn't a dream. It's a nightmare.
开萝尔:来,迈克,爬起来.
Carol: Come on Mike. Get out of bed.
迈克:嘿嘿,我没穿裤子.
Mike: Hey, hey. I don't have any pants on.
开萝尔:待在被窝里.
Carol: Stay in bed.
开萝尔:迈克,你每次晚回来而又没打电话,是怎么对爸爸妈妈说的?
Carol: Now Mike. What did you tell mum and dad, all those times you were late and didn't call?
迈克:没事,我只是偷偷摸摸地进来.
Mike: Nothing. I just snuck in.
开萝尔:但是如果他们希望你能早点回家呢?
Carol: But what if they expected you home a lot earlier?
迈克:开萝尔,他们要对付的是我,他们没指望我会早回家.你现在刚回家吗?
Mike: Carol, it was me they were dealing with. They didn't expect me home a lot earlier. Are you just getting home now?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Yes.
迈克:我的天哪.现在是十二点半了.怪不得爸爸说要杀了你.
Mike: Holy moly. It's twelve thirty. No wonder dad said he was going to kill you.
开萝尔:哦,不.
Carol: Oh no.
迈克:开个玩笑,我裤子也是个玩笑.
Mike: Just kidding. Just kidding about the pants too.
开萝尔:好的,现在我怎么向爸妈解释呢?
Carol: Alright. Now how am I going to explain this to mum and dad?
迈克:解释什么?你究竟干嘛去了?
Mike: Explain what? What the heck were you doing anyway?
开萝尔:不关你的事,我永远都不会告诉你的.
Carol: None of your business. I'm not telling you ever.
迈克:可能只是些无聊的事.
Mike: Yeah, probably be boring anyway.
开萝尔:说实话,我和一个男的出去了.你要说什么吗?
Carol: For your information, I was out with a man. What do you have to say to that?
迈克:开萝尔,我只是希望你决不要相信政府的密探.
Mike: Carol, I just hope that never in your life are you entrusted with government secrets.
开萝尔:我干嘛要来找你呢?
Carol: What did I come to you for?
迈克:嘿,别激动.我的意思是这不是个大问题.有个家伙选了你,这事总是要发生的,外面绝望孤独的家伙还多的是呢.
Mike: HHey, don't get so excited. I mean it's no big deal. So what, a guy picked up on you. It was bound to happen. There are plenty of desperately lonely guys out there.
开萝尔:我不是被选中,我们什么也没发生,说实话,我只是喝了一点葡萄酒.
Carol: I was not picked up. It was completely innocent. And for your information, I only had one sip of wine.
迈克:葡萄酒,喔.
Mike: Wine. Woooo.
开萝尔:只是出于礼貌,因为他比我大,我不是指很大,他是个大二学生.
Carol: Just to be polite because he was older. I mean not older, he was a sophomore.
迈克:嗯.
Mike: Uh hu.
开萝尔:他只是大我几岁.
Carol: Which is really only a couple of years older than I am.
迈克:当然,不会是一个脏兮兮的老头子.
Mike: But not old like a dirty old man.
开萝尔:你这只猪.
Carol: You're a pig.
迈克:(打一下嗝)谢谢你.
Mike: (burp) Thank you.
开萝尔:我只好去告诉爸爸妈妈实话了.
Carol: I am just going to tell mum and dad the truth.
迈克:哦.那会很好,开萝尔.
Mike: Oh yeah. That would be real good Carol.
开萝尔:我要告诉他们,我遇到了一个非常有趣的小伙子.
Carol: I'm going to tell that I met a real interesting guy.
迈克:他大概20多岁.
Mike: Who's probably in his twenties?
开萝尔:我们去聊天.
Carol: That we went to talk.
迈克:在一个酒吧里.
Mike: In a bar.
开萝尔:然后我忘了时间.
Carol: And that I lost track of time.
迈克:这和喝进肚子的葡萄酒无关.
Mike: Which had nothing to do with all the wine you knocked back.
开萝尔:只喝了一点点.女招待说要关门了,我跳进了车,以最快速度回了家.等一下,我可以证明,我甚至得了一张超速罚款单.哦,我的上帝!我不能告诉他们.
Carol: One little sip. And when the waitress said it was last call, I rushed in my car and drove home at top speed. Look, wait, I can prove it. I even got a speeding ticket. Oh my god! I can't tell them that.
迈克:开萝尔,你不需要担心你要怎么对爸妈说,我是说,你说什么他们都会相信.
Mike: Carol, look. You don't need to worry about what you are going to say to mum and dad. I mean, they'll believe anything you say.
开萝尔:你意思是?
Carol: What do you mean?
迈克:我们认为你是一个圣徒开萝尔.我是说你可以编造任何借口,他们都会相信的,你可以说你被一群牛缠住.
Mike: Look, they think of you as Saint Carol. I mean you could make up any excuse and they'd believe it. You could tell them that you were stuck in a herd of cattle.
开萝尔:告诉爸妈我被一群牛缠住!那就是你最好的建议?
Carol: Tell mum and dad I got stuck in a herd of cattle! That's your great advice?
迈克:是的,你说得对.如果你减了肥,它们就不会缠你了.
Mike: Yeah. You're right. They probably wouldn't buy that since you lost all that weight.
杰森:哦,谢谢你.黛比说她也不知道开萝尔的下落?
Jason: Ok, thank you. No Debbie doesn't know where she is either.
麦琪:哦,杰森,是不是她出了车祸?
Maggie: Oh Jason, what if she's been in an accident?
杰森:宝贝,别担心.可能是一些小事,你会为你的担心而感到好笑.
Jason: Honey, don't worry. It's probably some little thing so silly that you will laugh that you ever worried.
麦琪:好笑!
Maggie: Laugh!
杰森:哦,你会偷着乐.开萝尔,你好吗?
Jason: Ok, you'll chuckle. Carol. Are you OK?
开萝尔:嗯.
Carol: Uh hu.
杰森:你到底去哪儿了?图书馆三个半小时前就已经关门了.
Jason: Well then where the heck have you been? The library has been closed three and a half hours.
开萝尔:我真得很抱歉,因为我回家的路上碰上了一场严重的交通堵塞.
Carol: Well I'm really sorry but I ran into this huge traffic jam driving home.
麦琪:你为什么不打电话给我们?
Maggie: Why didn't you call us?
开萝尔:我找不到电话,我动都动不了.
Carol: I couldn't get to a phone. I could barely move.
麦琪:你困了三个小时.
Maggie: You were stuck in traffic for three hours.
开萝尔:嗯.
Carol: Uh hu.
杰森:出了什么问题?
Jason: What was the problem?
开萝尔:问题?
Carol: Problem.
麦琪:是什么让交通堵塞到半夜?
Maggie: What tied traffic up till midnight?
开萝尔:呃,牛.
Carol: Uh, cattle.
麦琪和杰森:牛?
Maggie and Jason: Cattle.
开萝尔:是的.那些运奶牛的卡车有一辆出了事故,奶牛跑上了大街.得把它们赶到一块,你知道这可是一群奶牛.
Carol: Yeah. One of those big trucks that carry cows got into an accident and cows were running all over the streets. It took forever to round them up. And you know how a herd of cattle can be.
杰森:奶牛上大街.我说过会是件搞笑的事.
Jason: Cows on the street. I told you it was something silly.
麦琪:开萝尔,我很高兴你平安归来.
Maggie: Carol. I'm just glad that you are safe.
开萝尔:毫发无损.
Carol: Safe and sound.
杰森:没有牛蹄踩上汽车吧?
Jason: No hoof prints on the car?
开萝尔:没有.
Carol: No.
麦琪:我想这车很难发动.
Maggie: Well I guess it was kind of hard to steer the car.
杰森:恐怕很难抓住方向盘.
Jason: Probably couldn't get your hands on the veal.
杰森:好的.
Jason: Ok.
麦琪:晚安,宝贝.
Maggie: Goodnight honey.
开萝尔:晚安,妈妈.
Carol: Night mum.
杰森:记得关灯.
Jason: Turn out the light.
开萝尔:我会的,爸爸.
Carol: I will dad.
麦琪:我们真应该装个汽车电话.
Maggie: This is exactly why we need a car phone.
杰森:只有好莱坞人才有汽车电话.
Jason: Only those Hollywood types have car phones.
开萝尔:是的!
Carol: Yes!
开萝尔:喂,桑迪.你的女性好朋友给你打电话喊你起床.喂,桑迪,你的女性好朋友给你打电话喊你起床.哦,不,开萝尔.我只是打电话说一声我昨晚过得很愉快,新的菲茨杰拉德传记!不,我还没见着.哦,我想看,但是我今晚必须待在家里看孩子.不,我是说我必须来宿舍回我父母的家,看他们的孩子,也就是我的小妹妹.你想来这儿!我是说那儿.我想不行.你稍等一下,妈妈,你们打算什么时候去看今晚的演出?
Carol: Hello Sandy. This is your friendly brunette wake up call. Hello. Sandy. This is your friendly finette cake up wall. Uh. No, Carol. I was just calling to say I had a really great time last night. The new Fitzgerald biography! No I haven't seen it. Oh, I'd love to, but I have to stay home and baby-sit tonight. No, I mean I have to leave my dorm and go over to my parents place and baby-sit one of their children. Who is also my baby sister. You want to come here! I mean there. I don't think I should. Will you hold on a second? Mum, what time are you guys leaving for the theatre tonight?
麦琪:我们得先把本送到维托家,大约是七点半吧.
Maggie: Well we have to drop Ben at Veto's first, so about seven thirty.
开萝尔:七点三十四怎么样?罗宾汉街15号,到时候见,再见.
Carol: How about seven thirty four? Fifteen Robin Hood lane. See you then. Au revoir.
杰森:你最好赶紧,本在眼馋你的法国面包呢.
Jason: You better hurry. Bens circling your French toast.
开萝尔:好的.
Carol: Ok then.
杰森:来,宝贝.早餐快凉了.
Jason: Come on honey. Breakfast is getting cold.
麦琪:马上下来.
Maggie: Be right down.
杰森:科格啤酒屋营业到半夜,欢迎学生光临.桑迪,5558321.啤酒屋!很好,很好,很好.
Jason: The Beer Keg. Open till midnight. Nightly, Student welcome. Sandy 5558321. The Beer keg! Well, well well.
本:你病了?
Ben: Are you sick or something?
开萝尔:不是,干嘛?
Carol: No. Why?
本:你看起来好像有锤子敲你的脑袋.
Ben: Well you look like someone just hit you in the head with a hammer.
开萝尔:我在思考,一个我相信你会困惑的概念.
Carol: I'm thinking. A concept I'm sure you would find confusing.
杰森:迈克还在吗?
Jason: Mike been in yet?
本:哦,他已经上学去了,怎么了?
Ben: Yeah, he already left for school. What's that?
杰森:枪在冒烟了.
Jason: The smoking gun.
本:科格啤酒屋.
Ben: Beer Keg.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
杰森:和你们没有关系.
Jason: Nothing that would concern either of you.
开萝尔:是吗?
Carol: It doesn't?
杰森:不,不,除非你们隐瞒你们的年龄,溜进酒吧.
Jason: No. Not unless you are lying about your age and sneaking into bars.
本:不是我.
Ben: Not me.
杰森:明摆着是迈克.他遇到了一个叫桑迪的女孩,要了她的电话号码.
Jason: Well, apparently Mike is. Met a girl names Sandy and got her phone number.
本:很好,迈克,真替他害臊,真不害臊.爸爸,要不我今晚不去维托家,而让他来我这儿,行吗?
Ben: Alright Mike. Shame shame shame. Dad, uh, instead of me going over to Veto tonight, would it be ok if I invited him over here?
开萝尔:不.我是说,你怎么想呢,爸爸?
Carol: No. I mean, well what do you think dad?
杰森:本,你知道规定.当你爸妈不在家时,不允许小孩子来家里.
Jason: Ben, you know the rules. When your parents aren't here, the kids aren't allowed to have anybody over.
本:但是维托妈妈不想让我们待在那儿.
Ben: But Veto mum doesn't want us over there.
杰森:为什么?
Jason: Why not?
本:我不知道,她担心我们会送她进精神病院,其实我还没驾照呢.
Ben: I don't know. She said something about us driving her round the bend. I don't even have a license.
杰森:那你就下次去找维托,今晚待在家里.
Jason: Well you'll just have to see Veto some other time. You're staying here tonight.
本:哦,不行.
Ben: Oh nuts.
杰森:你看你的姐姐就从不抱怨不能让朋友过来玩.
Jason: You don't see your sister complaining about not having somebody over.
开萝尔:爸爸,我有一个办法.你可以今晚把他送到斯汀奇家,爸爸,这样你们肯定可以扔下他去看戏.
Carol: Dad, I have an idea. Why don't you go over to Stinky's tonight? You know dad, I bet you could drop him off on your way to the play.
本:对!
Ben: Yeah!
杰森:好吧,我没问题,只是得先问问斯汀奇的爸妈.
Jason: Ok, well that's fine with me. Just check with Stinky's parents.
本:我马上给他们打电话.
Ben: I'll call them right now.
开萝尔:我得走了.
Carol: Well I got to run.
杰森:开萝尔,昨晚你是在图书馆吧?
Jason: Carol, were you at the library last night?
开萝尔:是的,我一直都在.
Carol: Yes, I was the entire time.
杰森:迈克在那儿吗?
Jason: And was Mike there?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Yes.
杰森:他真的在那儿?
Jason: Was he really there?
开萝尔:是的,他在.
Carol: Yes he was.
杰森:你不是要替他隐瞒吧?
Jason: So you are not just covering for him?
开萝尔:隐瞒?
Carol: Covering.
杰森:为了让他能够去啤酒吧?
Jason: Yes, so that he could go to this Beer bar?
开萝尔:不,不是,我看见他了.
Carol: No, no. I saw him.
杰森:好的,肯定有些其他原因.我该问什么呢?我知道你不会对我撒谎.
Jason: Well there must be some other explanation. What am I asking about? I knew that you wouldn't be lying to me.
开萝尔:不,我不会.再见.
Carol: No, no. I wouldn't. See ya.
麦琪:早上好,宝贝.
Maggie: Morning honey.
杰森:麦琪.嘿,昨晚我睡着时,你溜了出去,去了一家科格啤酒屋,遇到了一个叫桑迪的家伙?
Jason: Maggie. Hey when I was asleep last night, did you sneak out and go to a beer bar called the Beer Keg, and meet a guy named Sandy?
麦琪:谁告诉你的?
Maggie: Who told you?
开萝尔:快七点半了,你们要错过戏的开头了.
Carol: It's almost seven thirty. You're going to miss the beginning of the play.
麦琪:我总是不愿意离开小宝宝.
Maggie: I always hate to leave the baby.
杰森:是一部很棒的音乐剧,我想约 纳梅斯会让你惊喜的.
Jason: Well "Fiddler on the Roof" is a great musical and I think that Jo Nameth is going to surprise you.
本:很好,我准备去斯汀奇家.
Ben: Well, I'm ready to go to Stinky's.
开萝尔:好的,再见,好好看演出吧.
Carol: Well bye. Enjoy the show.
麦琪和杰森:再见.
Maggie and Jason: Bye.
麦琪:哦,开萝尔,我给了你……
Maggie: Oh Carol did I give you...
开萝尔:5552423,12排7座,8座.
Carol: Five five five two four two three, row twelve, seat seven and eight.
麦琪:好的,晚安,宝贝.
Maggie: Ok, good night honey.
开萝尔:真不知道迈克是怎么干的,我太紧张了.
Carol: I don't know how Mike does it. I cannot take this tension.
迈克:妈妈,爸爸,有需要我做的家务活吗?
Mike: Mum, dad. Anything I can do to help around the house.
开萝尔:迈克,他们走了,我也没钱,再见.
Carol: Save it Mike. They are gone and I don't have any money either. Good bye.
迈克:嘿,看看这.他们把你关禁闭,打扫房间.你得做多久?一星期,还是两星期?
Mike: Hey, look at this. They even made you clean the house while you were grounded. So, what did you get? One week, two weeks?
开萝尔:不用,我采纳了你的建议,他们相信了我,谢谢你,你可以走了.
Carol: No weeks. I took your advice and they believed me. Now thank you and get out.
迈克:什么借口?
Mike: What excuse?
开萝尔:关于牛的.
Carol: The one about the cattle.
迈克:开萝尔,我只是挖苦而已,我,我,他们相信这?
Mike: Carol, I was being sarcastic, I, I, they bought that?
开萝尔:完全相信,你现在能走吗?
Carol: Totally. Now would you just go!
迈克:等等,等等.要我跑步出去?
Mike: Wait, wait, wait. Now what the big rush?
开萝尔:不用跑步,只要轻轻地离开.
Carol: There's no rush. Just leave.
迈克:嗯.你有人要来.
Mike: Uh hu. You got somebody coming over.
开萝尔:我不知道你在说什么?
Carol: I have no idea what you are talking about.
迈克:他是一个男人.就是你昨晚约会的那个男人.喔!爸爸妈妈知道你约了那个讨厌的家伙来我们家吗?
Mike: And it's a guy. The guy you partied with last night. Wo ho! So, does mum and dad know that you've got this nerd coming over?
开萝尔:他们没有提到.
Carol: Well it didn't come up in the conversation.
迈克:很好,你开始像我一样瞒天过海了,开萝尔,你真的要走上歧途了.
Mike: Well, you're starting to cut corners just like me. Carol, you are really coming over to the dark side.
开萝尔:他只是来借给我一本书.
Carol: He's just coming over to lend me a book.
迈克:是的.他是谁,一个图书馆?
Mike: Yeah right. What is he, a library?
开萝尔:迈克,你不会说什么的,对吧?
Carol: Mike, you're not going to say anything, are you?
迈克:我!开萝尔.我不是一个喜欢告密的人,事实是,我相当羡慕你.所以,我得走了.
Mike: Me! Come on Carol. I am not a snitch. As a matter of fact, I kind of admire what you got going here. So um, I'll just be on my way.
开萝尔:谢谢.
Carol: Thanks.
迈克:只要有人愿意把我的英语家庭作业打成字.
Mike: As soon as I find someone to type my English homework.
开萝尔:我向爸爸撒谎,替你摆脱麻烦,你还这样对我?
Carol: You have the nerve to do this to me after I lied to dad to get you out of trouble?
迈克:什么麻烦?
Mike: What trouble?
开萝尔:我说你去了图书馆,不让他们知道你去了酒吧.
Carol: Saying that you went to the library just so that you could go to that bar.
迈克:不,我没有去酒吧,你去了.
Mike: No. I did not go to that bar. You did.
开萝尔:老天,是这样.我分不清谎言和事实了.我到底怎么了?
Carol: Gosh. That's right. I don't know a lie from the truth anymore. What's happening to me.
(门铃声)
(Door bell)
迈克:我去开门.
Mike: I'll get that.
开萝尔:好的,好的.我替你打字,该死的英语论文,只要你马上离开.
Carol: Alright, alright. I'll type your stupid English paper for you if you just leave right now.
迈克:隔行打?
Mike: Double spaced?
开萝尔:行.
Carol: Yes.
迈克:不要拼错.
Mike: No misspelled words?
开萝尔:走吧.
Carol: Go.
迈克:成交.你生意做成了,开萝尔.
Mike: Deal. You drive a hard bargain Carol.
开萝尔:记得锁门.酸球糖满地都是!我要变成一个傻瓜了,不值得,真是不值.你好.
Carol: And lock the door behind you. Sour balls all over the floor! I'm turning into a slob. Do it. It's not worth it. It is just not worth it. It's worth it. Hi.
桑迪:我把书带来了.
Sandy: I brought that book.
开萝尔:书?哦,谢谢.
Carol: What book. Oh, gee. Thanks.
桑迪:嗯,我可以进来吗?
Sandy: Eh, can I come in?
开萝尔:哦,我很抱歉,当然可以,你可以进来.
Carol: Oh yeah. I'm sorry. Of course. Course you can come in.
桑迪:喔,这是你父母的房子?
Sandy: Wow, this is your parent's house hu?
开萝尔:是的.
Carol: Yeah.
桑迪:他们在吗?我很想见他们.
Sandy: Well, where are they? I'd love to meet them.
开萝尔:哦,他们走了,我的兄弟也走了,每个人都走了.
Carol: Oh, they're gone. My brothers are gone. Everybody's...gone.
桑迪:哦.
Sandy: Oh.
麦琪:杰森,我要进去了.
Maggie: Jason, I am going inside.
开萝尔:我的爸妈!藏到椅子后面.
Carol: My parents! Behind the chair.
桑迪:什么?
Sandy: What?
开萝尔:藏起来.
Carol: Hide.
桑迪:为什么?
Sandy: Why?
杰森:我待会进去.
Jason: I'll be in in a minute.
开萝尔:因为我爸爸很疯狂,拿着把枪,哦,妈妈,你们怎么回家了?
Carol: Because my father's insane and he carries a gun. Oh mum. What are you doing home?
麦琪:哦,车开不了了,等到修好恐怕看不了演出了.
Maggie: Oh, the car died and by the time we got it going we were too late for the play.
开萝尔:哦,太可惜了.
Carol: Oh what a shame.
麦琪:哦,开萝尔,别告诉你的爸爸,我其实不介意是否看约 纳梅斯的.
Maggie: Oh Carol, don't tell your dad, but I don't care if I ever see Jo Nameth Fiddler on the Roof.
开萝尔:他在哪儿?
Carol: Where is he?
麦琪:我想他正在舞台中央,唱着"如果我是一个有钱人".
Maggie: Oh imagine about right now, he's centre stage trying to sing "if I were a rich man".
开萝尔:不,我是说爸爸?
Carol: No, I mean where's dad?
麦琪:他在找汽修账单,我想那个机修师没有给汽车换新的火花塞,你爸爸正发火呢.要是他认为有人想占他便宜,他就会这样.
Maggie: Oh he's looking for the mechanics bill. I guess the mechanic didn't put new spark plugs in the car, and your father's fuming. You know how he gets when he thinks someone's trying to pull a fast one on him.
开萝尔:哦,是的.
Carol: Oh yeah.
麦琪:宝贝,我们出去时家里没开灯吗?
Maggie: Honey, was the house dark when we drove up?
开萝尔:没有.
Carol: No, no.
杰森:不在手套的格子里,我得去办公室看看.
Jason: It's not in the glove compartment. I'll be looking in the office.
麦琪:杰森,别担心.你会要回你的钱的.
Maggie: Jason, don't worry about it. You'll get your money back.
杰森:哦,那不是钱的问题,麦琪.是的,就是钱.但是我痛恨有人对我撒谎.
Jason: Oh, it's not the money Maggie. Yes it is the money. But I hate being lied to even more.
麦琪:我得去看看克莉丝.
Maggie: I'm going to peek in on Chrissy.
开萝尔:很遗憾车出问题了.
Carol: Sorry about the car dad.
杰森:我只是替你妈妈感到遗憾,你知道她很喜欢约 纳梅斯.
Jason: I just feel sorry for your mother. You know what a Jo Nameth fan she is.
桑迪:哦,你是对的,他真的是个疯子.
Sandy: Wow, you're right. He really is nuts.
开萝尔:后门.
Carol: The back door.
开萝尔:不,不,起来.
Carol: No, no. Get up.
杰森:开萝尔?
Jason: Carol?
开萝尔:是的,爸爸.
Carol: Yeah dad.
杰森:你在说什么?
Jason: Did you say something?
开萝尔:没什么,爸爸.
Carol: No dad.
杰森:哦.
Jason: Oh.
开萝尔:哦,很抱歉,都是这些酸球糖.你还好吧?
Carol: Oh. Sorry about the sour balls. Are you ok?
桑迪:我只想离开这儿.
Sandy: I just want to get out of here.
麦琪:杰森,我去给我们泡些茶.
Maggie: Jason, I'll make us some tea.
开萝尔:跟我来!
Carol: Come on!
桑迪:门锁住了,钥匙在哪?
Sandy: It's locked. Where's the key?
开萝尔:别慌.
Carol: Don't panic.
桑迪:哦,你说得容易,你父亲不会杀了你.
Sandy: Oh, easy for you to say. Your father's not going to shoot you.
开萝尔:别站在那儿,他们会看见你.
Carol: Not there. They'll see you.
麦琪:走廊很乱.
Maggie: This hallway's a mess.
开萝尔:我让本打扫的.
Carol: I told Ben to clean it up.
麦琪:你应该确认一下.你爸爸在哪呢?
Maggie: You sure will. Where's your father?
开萝尔:在办公室里.我来扫,我来给你们泡茶.
Carol: In the office. I'll do that. I'll make you tea.
麦琪:哦,很好,开萝尔.你没责任,很抱歉我们搅乱了你的周末.
Maggie: Oh that's ok Carol. You're off duty. Sorry we messed up your Friday night.
开萝尔:哦,不,你们没有,一点也没有.
Carol: Oh no, you didn't. Not at all.
麦琪:现在才八点半.如果你想的话你还可以出去.
Maggie: You know it's only eight thirty. You could still go out if you want to.
开萝尔:哦,我很好.
Carol: Oh I'm fine. Just fine.
杰森:啊!酸球糖.地上到处都是.
Jason: Ahhhhh! Sour balls. They are all over the floor in there.
麦琪:哦,杰森!你没事吧?
Maggie: Oh Jason! Are you alright?
杰森:看,我找到了一张收条,都在这儿呢,六个新火花塞.看!
Jason: Look I found a receipt and it's all there. Six new spark plugs. Look!
麦琪:杰森,我相信你.冲着机修师发火,别冲着我.
Maggie: Jason I believe you. Yell at the mechanic, not me.
杰森:你知道谁惹火了我?这家伙以为我不注意.想一想,有人想占我便宜,而我就站在那.
Jason: You know what gripes me? The guy thought I wouldn't notice. Imagine the nerve of somebody trying to pull a fast one and me standing right there.
开萝尔:爸爸,爸爸.我有一个办法.你去客厅,我泡茶给你喝.
Carol: Dad dad. I have an idea. Why don't you go into the living room, and I'll bring you your tea.
杰森:你不能相信任何人.
Jason: You can't trust anybody anymore.
桑迪:啊!请不要对我开枪.
Sandy: Ahhh! Please don't shoot me.
开萝尔:你们茶里要放塘吗?
Carol: So do you guys want sugar in your tea?
迈克:开萝尔,你究竟在做什么
Mike: Carol, what the heck are you doing...
开萝尔:打你该死的英语论文.我说我会的,我正在做呢.
Carol: Typing your stupid English paper. I said I would, and I am.
迈克:我还没写呢.
Mike: I didn't even start writing it yet.
开萝尔:很好,我已经不能让任何人满意了.
Carol: Fine, I can't please anyone lately.
迈克:你尝试一下女人的手段?
Mike: Look. Are you going through one of them female deals?
开萝尔:我刚和爸爸妈妈大吵了一架.
Carol: I just had a major fight with mum and dad.
迈克:哦,他们在家?
Mike: Oh yeah. Are they home?
开萝尔:是的.他们让我回自己的房间,但是我不去.
Carol: Oh yeah. And they sent me to my room, but I refused to go.
迈克:哦,所以他们知道你偷偷约了一个男人?
Mike: Oh, so they caught you with that guy that you were sneaking in.
开萝尔:是的,我全对他们说了.酒吧,葡萄酒,牛,超速罚款单,酸球糖.你知道他们打算做什么吗?
Carol: Yes, and I told them about everything. The bar, the wine, the cattle, the speeding ticket, the sour balls. And do you know what they had the nerve to do?
迈克:不知道,什么呢?
Mike: No, what?
开萝尔:他们关我三星期禁闭.
Carol: They grounded me for three weeks.
迈克:我也这么想.
Mike: Well I guess so.
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
迈克:来,开萝尔,一个他们总是信任的西维尔家的孩子,突然背叛了他们.
Mike: Come on Carol. The one Seaver kid that they can always trust just went over to the enemy.
开萝尔:没有人十全十美.
Carol: Yow! Well nobody's perfect.
迈克:没有人.
Mike: Not anymore.
开萝尔:你说爸妈相信我,所以我闯了祸也和你不一样?
Carol: Are you saying that it's different when I mess up because mum and dad actually trust me, unlike you?
迈克:是的,我很抱歉,我得去做家庭作业了.现在走了.
Mike: No. I'm sorry, I got homework to do. Now get out.
开萝尔:你说得对.他们相信我.
Carol: You're right. They trusted me.
迈克:嗯.
Mike: Uh hu.
开萝尔:他们总是相信我,现在我却对他们做了这样的事情.
Carol: They've always trusted me and now I do something like this to them.
迈克:嘿.你可以去自己的房间唠叨吗?
Mike: Hey look. Could you go babble in your own room?
杰森:迈克,你妈妈和我想和你妹妹谈谈.
Jason: Mike, your mother and I would like to have a word with your sister.
迈克:好的.
Mike: Fine.
杰森:单独谈.
Jason: Alone.
迈克:把她带走吧.
Mike: Take her away.
麦琪:你可以离开吗?
Maggie: Could you leave?
迈克:嘿,这是我的地盘.
Mike: Hey, this is my own apartment.
杰森:你想待在这?
Jason: You want to keep it?
迈克:是的,但是如果我完不成我的英语作业,你们要负责.
Mike: Right, but if I mess up my English assignment, it's on your heads.
麦琪:开萝尔,我们去你的房间.
Maggie: Carol, we sent you to your room.
杰森:如果你还这么大声音的话,我要关你三个月禁闭.我们继续中断的谈话吧.
Jason: And if you raise your voice, it will be three months grounding. Now let's go back to where we left off.
开萝尔:我很抱歉.
Carol: I'm sorry.
杰森:你不应该这样.
Jason: Well you should be young lady.
开萝尔:我不想发火.我想我刚才生气是因为我不愿意相信我会和迈克一样,但是现在我确实更糟.
Carol: Look, I didn't mean to yell. I guess I was just angry because I didn't want to believe that I was as slimy as Mike, but now I see I was worse.
杰森:是的,你理解了.
Jason: Yeah, well what you got to understand.
开萝尔:我理解你们为什么对我发火.你们对我真的很失望,我辜负了你们的信任.
Carol: And I understand why you were yelling at me. I mean you were really disappointed in me. I've betrayed your trust.
麦琪:是的,但是重要的是.
Maggie: Yes, but what's important here.
开萝尔:我以前从来没有这样,至少不会这么严重,我想在这种情况下,我理解你们为什么关我三个星期禁闭.
Carol: And I have never done that before. At least not for something as serious as this. So I guess under the circumstances, I understand why you grounded me for three weeks.
杰森:很好,我很高兴我们能有这次谈话.
Jason: Well uh, I'm glad we can have this little talk.
开萝尔:你想说什么吗?
Carol: You wanted to say something?
杰森:嗯,我想现在我们已经没事了.
Jason: Uh, I think we've pretty much covered it now.
开萝尔:我很难过.
Carol: I'm sorry.
麦琪:哦,宝贝,没什么了.我不是说很好,我是说,你应该明白我的意思.
Maggie: Oh honey, that's ok. I mean it's not Ok. I mean. You know what I mean.
杰森:希望你下次想约小伙子的时候,告诉我们.我是说……
Jason: And hopefully you'll let us know the next time you want to sneak a guy in. I mean...
开萝尔:我知道你们的意思.妈妈,爸爸,不会再有下次了.相信我.
杰森:我想我们终于学会了如何做父母.
00:23:08,200
Carol: I know what you mean. And mum, dad, it won't ever happen again. Trust me. Jason: Well I think we are finally getting the hang of this parenting business.